<GameData><LocalizedText>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_ABILITY_AUTOMATIC_GUNFIRE_DESCRIPTION"><Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Melee, Anti Cavalry and Light Cavalry units.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_ABILITY_CITY_CENTER_NERF_DESCRIPTION"><Text>-6 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Districts.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_ABILITY_EXPLORER_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Ignores rivers when moving and has no disembark cost.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PLUS_X_WHEN_DEFENDING_DESCRIPTION"><Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when defending.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PRE_GUNPOWDER_MELEE_ATTACK_DESCRIPTION"><Text>+6 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against pre-Gunpowder Melee units on non-District tiles.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_COG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>A cog is a type of ship that first appeared in the 10th century, and was widely used from around the 12th century on. Cogs were clinker-built, generally of oak, which was an abundant timber in the Baltic region of Prussia. This vessel was fitted with a single mast and a square-rigged single sail. These vessels were mostly associated with seagoing trade in medieval Europe, especially the Hanseatic League, particularly in the Baltic Sea region. They ranged from about 15 to 25 meters (49 to 82 ft) in length with a beam of 5 to 8 meters (16 to 26 ft), and the largest cog ships could carry up to about 200 tons. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_COG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_COG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_COG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_COG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>Los coraceros eran jinetes de melé armados con sable y protegidos por corazas y casco de hierro que formaban un cuerpo de caballería pesada aparecida en Europa en el último tercio del siglo XV. Los primeros coraceros fueron sucesores de los caballeros medievales, de los que no distinguían mucho, ya que también llevaban armadura completa. Se diferenciaban sólo por el uso de pistolas y botas de montar. Gradualmente los coraceros disminuyeron la cantidad de piezas de la armadura para obtener sólo la coraza y los cascos de hierro. Particularmente famosos fueron los regimientos de coraceros franceses ("cuirassiers", en francés) usados durante las Guerras Napoleónicas en casi todos los teatros de guerra. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_EXPLORER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>La era de los descubrimientos fue un período histórico que dio comienzo a principios del siglo XV extendiéndose hasta comienzos del siglo XVIII. Durante esta época los europeos, principalmente portugueses, españoles y británicos, recorrieron casi la totalidad del Planeta, cartografiándolo y conquistándolo en buena medida. El motivo de dicha expansión vino por la necesidad de acceder a las riquezas de Asia con las cuales contribuir al mercantilismo europeo, pero la causa o causas últimas siguen siendo discutidas. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_EXPLORER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text>La exploración global comenzó con los descubrimientos portugueses de los archipiélagos de Maderia y las Azores en el Atlántico, la costa de África, y el descubrimiento de la ruta por mar a la India en 1498; y, en nombre de la Corona de Castilla, el Pasaje trans-Atlántico de Cristóbal Colón entre 1492 y 1502, y la primera circunnavegación del globo en 1519-1522. Estos descubrimientos condujeron a numerosas expediciones navales a través de los océanos Atlántico, Indio y Pacífico, y expediciones por tierra en las Américas, Asia, África, y Australia que continuaron durante el siglo XIX, y terminaron con la exploración de las regiones polares en el siglo XX. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_EXPLORER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_EXPLORER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_EXPLORER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GALLEASS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>Galleasses were military ships developed from large merchant galleys. Converted for military use, they were higher, larger and slower than regular ("light") galleys. They had up to 32 oars, each worked by up to 5 men. They usually had three masts and a forecastle and aftcastle. Much effort was made in Venice to make these galleasses as fast as possible to compete with regular galleys. The gun deck usually ran over the rowers' heads, but there are also pictures showing the opposite arrangement. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GALLEASS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text>Galleasses usually carried more sails than true galleys and were far deadlier; a galley caught broadside lay all but helpless, since coming broadside to a galleass, as with a ship of the line, exposed an attacker to her gunfire. Relatively few galleasses were built—one disadvantage was that, being more reliant on sails, their position at the front of the galley line at the start of a battle could not be guaranteed—but they were used at the Battle of Lepanto in 1571, their firepower helping to win victory for the Holy League fleet, and some sufficiently seaworthy galleasses accompanied the Spanish Armada in 1588 (e.g. La Girona). In the 15th century, a type of light galleass, called the frigate, was built in southern European countries to answer the increasing challenge posed by the North African-based Barbary pirates in their fast galleys. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GALLEASS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text>In the Mediterranean, with its less dangerous weather and fickle winds, both galleasses and galleys continued to be in use, particularly in Venice and the Ottoman Empire, long after they became obsolete elsewhere. Later, "round ships" and galleasses were replaced by galleons and ships of the line which originated in Atlantic Europe. The first Venetian ship of the line was built in 1660. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GALLEASS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GALLEASS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GATLING_GUN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>The Gatling gun is one of the best-known early rapid-fire spring loaded, hand cranked weapons and a forerunner of the modern machine gun. Invented by Richard Gatling, it is known for its use by the Union forces during the American Civil War in the 1860s, which was the first time it was employed in combat. Later, it was used again in numerous military conflicts, such as the Boshin War, the Anglo-Zulu War, and the assault on San Juan Hill during the Spanish–American War. It was also used by militias and the National Guard in episodes of the Great Railroad Strike of 1877, specifically in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GATLING_GUN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text>The Gatling gun's operation centered on a cyclic multi-barrel design which facilitated cooling and synchronized the firing-reloading sequence. Each barrel fired a single shot when it reached a certain point in the cycle, after which it ejected the spent cartridge, loaded a new round, and, in the process, allowed the barrel to cool somewhat. This configuration allowed higher rates of fire to be achieved without the barrels overheating. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GATLING_GUN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GATLING_GUN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_GATLING_GUN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_LONGSWORDSMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>La espada larga era el arma más versátil del campo de batalla medieval/renacentista. Era más ligera y fácil de llevar que una pica, y podía ser usada a una o dos manos, haciendo posible que un espadachín pueda llevar un escudo. En combate cara-a-cara contra piqueros los espadachines estaban a una desventaja significativa, tomando muchas bajas debido a las armas más largas antes de poder entrar en distancia de ataque. Sin embargo, los espadachines eran más rápidos y maniobrables que los piqueros - y si les podían dar por el flanco, los piqueros eran carne muerta. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_LONGSWORDSMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_LONGSWORDSMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_LONGSWORDSMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_LONGSWORDSMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MORTAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>A mortar is a device that fires projectiles at low velocities and short ranges. The mortar has traditionally been used as a weapon to propel explosive mortar bombs in high-arcing ballistic trajectories. The weapon is typically muzzle-loading with a short, often smooth-bore barrel, generally less than 15 times its caliber. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MORTAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MORTAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MORTAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_MORTAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_RIFLEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>El rifle es un arma de fuego diseñado para ser disparado desde el hombro. El interior del barril ha sido rayada de manera helicoidal para que el proyectil gire cuando se dispare, confiriéndole mayor rango y precisión que uno sin rayar. Los primeros intentos de rayar barriles en Europa ocurrieron en el siglo XV, pero dificultades en la fabricación lo mantuvieron lejos del uso general hasta el siglo XIX. Los fronterizos americanos tenían rifles en la Guerra de la Independencia Americana. Vanguardia británica y americana, y exploradores estaban equipados con mosquetes rayados durante la Guerra Napoleónica y la Guerra de 1812, pero el tiempo de carga más lento del arma la mantuvo lejos de las manos de la infantería estándar durante varios años. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_RIFLEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text>La invención de la "bala Minié" redujo extremadamente el tiempo de recarga, y al llegar la guerra civil estadounidense mosquetes rayados estaban incluidos en la mayoría de ejércitos europeos. Al final de la guerra civil el mosquete se volvió obsoleto ante el rifle de repetición de retrocarga, que poseía una cadencia de disparo de tal vez un disparo por segundo (tan rápido como uno pudiera amartillar la palanca y disparar), comparado con los fusiles de pedernal que tenían una cadencia de 20 a 30 segundos por disparo para un soldado bien entrenado. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_RIFLEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_RIFLEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_RIFLEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>Self-propelled artillery (also called mobile artillery or locomotive artillery) is artillery equipped with its own propulsion system to move towards its target. Within the term are covered self-propelled guns (or howitzers) and rocket artillery. They are high mobility vehicles, usually based on continuous tracks carrying either a large howitzer, field gun, a mortar or some form of rocket or missile launcher. They are usually used for long-range indirect bombardment support on the battlefield. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text>In the past, self-propelled artillery has included direct-fire vehicles, such as assault guns and tank destroyers. These have been heavily armoured vehicles, the former providing close fire-support for infantry and the latter acting as specialized anti-tank vehicles. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text>Modern self-propelled artillery vehicles may superficially resemble tanks, but they are generally lightly armoured, too lightly to survive in direct-fire combat. However, they protect their crews against shrapnel and small arms and are therefore usually included as armoured fighting vehicles. Many are equipped with machine guns for defense against enemy infantry. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text>The key advantage of self-propelled over towed artillery is that it can be brought into action much faster. Before the towed artillery can be used, it has to stop, unlimber and set up the guns. To move position, the guns must be limbered up again and brought—usually towed—to the new location. By comparison, self-propelled artillery can stop at a chosen location and begin firing almost immediately, then quickly move on to a new position. This shoot-and-scoot ability is very useful in a mobile conflict and particularly on the advance. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_TREBUCHET_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"><Text>The trebuchet is a powerful Medieval siege weapon. First appearing in Europe in the 12th century, the trebuchet could hurl a 300-lb missile into or over the enemy's walls at long distance. The Medieval European version of the trebuchet was a "counterweight" machine. It consisted of a very long wooden arm with a sling on one end and a heavy weight on the other, mounted on a heavy wooden framework. The long arm was winched down, raising the heavy weight, and a missile was placed in the sling. When released, the weight would come down and the arm would whip up into the air, hurling the missile a huge distance. These machines were generally not mobile and required a long process of assembly, limiting their effective use to protracted sieges. </Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_TREBUCHET_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_TREBUCHET_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_TREBUCHET_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DLV_TREBUCHET_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5"><Text/></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_COG_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Medieval Era Naval Melee unit.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_COG_NAME"><Text>Cog</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Unidad de caballería pesada de la edad industrial</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_DLV_CUIRASSIER_NAME"><Text>Coracero (Cuirassier)</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_EXPLORER_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Unidad del renacimiento de reconocimiento con movimiento rapido. Ignora los rios y no tiene penalizacion al movimiento al desembarcar</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_EXPLORER_NAME"><Text>Explorador</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_GALLEASS_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Medieval Era Naval Ranged unit. +8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when defending.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_GALLEASS_NAME"><Text>Galleass</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_GATLING_GUN_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Unidad anti-caballería de la edad industrial. Se mejora desde piquero. Se mejora a tripulación antitanque.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_GATLING_GUN_NAME"><Text>Ametralladora Gatling</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_LONGSWORDSMAN_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Unidad medieval de combate cuerpo a cuerpo.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_LONGSWORDSMAN_NAME"><Text>Guerrero con espada larga</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_MACHINE_GUN_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Atomic era Ranged unit. +8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Melee, Anti Cavalry and Light Cavalry units.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Caballeria ligera de la edad medieval</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_MEDIEVAL_HORSEMAN_NAME"><Text>Montaraz</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_MORTAR_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Atomic era Ranged unit.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_MORTAR_NAME"><Text>Mortar</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_RIFLEMAN_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Unidad cuerpo a cuerpo de la edad industrial</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_RIFLEMAN_NAME"><Text>Fusilero</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_ROCKET_ARTILLERY_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Information era Ranged unit.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_ROCKET_ARTILLERY_NAME"><Text>Rocket Launcher</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Information era Siege unit.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_SELF_PROPELLED_ARTILLERY_NAME"><Text>Self Propelled Artillery</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_TREBUCHET_DESCRIPTION"><Text>Medieval Siege unit.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="LOC_UNIT_TREBUCHET_NAME"><Text>Trebuchet</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="MINUS_X_VS_CITY_CENTERS_DESC"><Text>-6 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Districts.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="PLUS_15_VS_LIGHT_CAVALRY_COMBAT_BONUS_DESC"><Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength versus Light Cavalry.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="PLUS_20_VS_HEAVY_CAVALRY_COMBAT_BONUS_DESC"><Text>+20 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength versus Heavy Cavalry.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="PLUS_X_VS_MELEE_ANTICAV_LIGHTCAV_COMBAT_BONUS_DESC"><Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Melee, Anti Cavalry and Light Cavalry units.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="PLUS_X_VS_PRE_GUNPOWDER_MELEE_DESC"><Text>+6 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against pre-Gunpowder Melee units on non-District tiles.</Text></Replace>
<Replace Language="es_ES" Tag="PLUS_X_WHEN_DEFENDING_DESC"><Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when defending.</Text></Replace>
</LocalizedText></GameData>
